const beforeInterviewFlashcards = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Analyze the Job Description",
    answer:
      "Before your interview, take the time to thoroughly review the job description. By understanding the qualifications and background the company seeks, you can better present yourself as the ideal candidate. The job posting might also provide insights into potential interview questions.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "Investigate the Company",
    answer:
      "To be well-prepared for the interview, conduct research on the company. Understand its industry, key players, products and services, target customers, and - most importantly - its culture, mission, and values. This knowledge will boost your confidence and comfort level during the interview.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Clarify Your Objectives",
    answer:
      "Ensure you have a solid understanding of why you want the job and why the company should hire you. Be prepared to articulate your interest in the position and explain why you are the best fit for the role. Additionally, have your short-term and long-term goals for the position in mind, as these may be discussed during the interview.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Practice Common Interview Questions",
    answer:
      "Familiarize yourself with typical interview questions and practice your responses. This preparation will help you feel more at ease and confident during the actual interview.",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "Prepare Your Resume",
    answer:
      "Bring several copies of your resume to the interview, as the interviewer may not have it readily available. Print three to four copies in case there are multiple interviewers, and keep a copy for yourself to reference during the conversation.",
  },
];

const duringInterviewFlashcards = [
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Dress Professionally",
    answer:
      "Aim to dress one level higher than the average employee. For example, if you are applying for an entry-level job, dress for an intermediate-level position. Supervisors may dress similarly to high-level managers or directors. Ensure your clothing is free of stains or wrinkles and that your shoes are polished. Keep jewelry minimal.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Make a Checklist",
    answer:
      "Bring the following items to your interview: multiple copies of your resume (3-4), a pen, a notepad, a printout of your professional references, a professional-looking bag, and a portfolio (if applicable). Although you can bring your phone, keep it on mute and store it in your bag during the interview. Avoid wearing strong perfume or cologne, as the interviewer may be sensitive to potent odors.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Arrive Early",
    answer:
      "Punctuality is highly valued. Confirm your arrival via text and arrive at the venue 10 minutes before your scheduled appointment. Arriving too early may disrupt the interviewer's schedule and create a negative impression. If you arrive earlier than planned, wait in your car or a nearby caf√© until the appropriate time.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Listen",
    answer:
      "Although the goal of an interview is to answer questions, ensure you are actively listening to the interviewer. Failing to pay attention can result in canned or irrelevant responses. Listening helps build rapport and facilitates a smoother conversation. If you have questions, ask them once the interviewer has finished, and take notes of any important points you want to remember.",
  },
];

const onlineInterviewFlashcards = [
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "Research the Company",
    answer:
      "Gather as much information as possible about the company to feel more prepared and confident during the interview. Look into the industry, products/services, location, mission, vision, culture, history, major successes, and names of owners/managers. Start with the company's website and follow their social media pages for additional insights.",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: "Identify Your Most Sellable Skills",
    answer:
      "Review the job listing thoroughly to ensure you possess the required skills. List three to five of your most relevant or transferrable skills to demonstrate your qualifications for the position. Practice describing your key achievements and be prepared to explain why you are the best candidate for the job, your interest in it, and your professional goals if hired. Core skills employers often seek include time management, organization, attention to detail, mastery of relevant technology, and teamwork.",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: "Pick the Perfect Spot",
    answer:
      "Choose a quiet, well-lit location for your online interview. If possible, use a spot near a window with natural sunlight for a warm glow. Avoid areas that are too dark or have heavy foot traffic. Consider staging the space with books or artwork for a sophisticated appearance, or use a solid-colored wall as a backdrop.",
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    question: "Dress for Success",
    answer:
      "Dress as formally as you would for an in-person interview, including pants and shoes. Fully dressing helps create a professional image and mentally prepares you for the interview. Opt for neutral-colored, professional-looking attire and try on your outfit beforehand to ensure it looks good on camera.",
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    question: "Test Your Hardware/Software",
    answer:
      "Reduce the chance of connection failure or errors by testing your setup ahead of time. Test the app, hardware, and internet connection with a friend or family member via video chat. Ensure the microphone and speakers work, the audio is clear without background noise, the video has proper lighting, and there are no distracting objects around you. Familiarize yourself with basic app functions, such as muting and unmuting the microphone and turning the video on and off.",
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    question: "Avoid Using Virtual Backgrounds",
    answer:
      "Virtual backgrounds can be distracting for interviewers, so it is highly recommended to use a natural environment as your backdrop. Only use virtual backgrounds as a last resort.",
  },
  {
    id: "16",
    question: "Get Rid of Distractions",
    answer:
      "Eliminate interruptions during your interview. Mute notifications and any app that could activate during your call. Secure your pets and inform household members to avoid the interview spot. If you cannot guarantee a disruption-free environment, consider another location or inform the interviewer about potential interruptions. Interviewers will appreciate your honesty and understand the challenges you face.",
  },
  {
    id: "17",
    question: "Log On a Few Minutes Early",
    answer:
      "Logging in early demonstrates that you value the interviewer's time and allows you to calm your nerves and confirm everything is working properly. Be visible on the app at least five minutes before your scheduled interview. Prepare your device by closing extra apps, recheck the video and audio quality, and consider doing a brief meditation to prepare yourself.",
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    question: 'Follow Up',
    answer: 'Following up after the interview demonstrates your genuine interest in the job. Send an email within a day or two, thanking the interviewer for their time and expressing your enthusiasm for the position after learning more during the conversation. Include topics discussed during the interview to personalize your email follow-up and leave a lasting impression.'
    }
];

export {
  beforeInterviewFlashcards,
  duringInterviewFlashcards,
  onlineInterviewFlashcards,
};
